Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
Raymond Moley papers
1902-1971.
68008
Moley, Raymond, 1886-1975.
256 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize boxes, 35 card file boxes, 1 oversize folder, 5 envelopes, 3 phonotape reels. (118 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, diaries, reports, memoranda, speeches and writings, notes, printed matter, and photographs, relating to criminology and the administration of justice, assimilation of immigrants, politics in the United States, the presidential campaign of 1932, the administration of Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Today and Newsweek magazines. Sound use copies of sound recordings available.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1968.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, diaries, reports, memoranda, speeches and writings, notes, printed matter, and photographs, relating to criminology and the administration of justice, assimilation of immigrants, politics in the United States, the presidential campaign of 1932, the administration of Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Today and Newsweek magazines.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Democratic Party (U.S.); Republican Party (U.S.: 1854-); Journalism--United States.; Presidents--United States--Election--1932; United States--Economic policy.; United States--Politics and government--1933-1945.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.; United States--Social conditions.; Justice, Administration of--United States.; Criminology--United States.; Americanization.; United States--Emigration and immigration.; Journalists.; Phonotapes.; Newsweek.; Today.
Biographical Note
1886, September 27 Born, Berea, Ohio
1906 Ph.B., Baldwin-Wallace College
1913 A.M., Oberlin College
1916-1919 Instructor and Assistant Professor of Politics, Western Reserve University
1917 Author, Lessons in American Citizenship
1918 Ph.D., Columbia University Author, The State Movement for Efficiency and Economy
1919 Author, Lessons in Democracy Author, Commercial Recreation
1919-1923 Director, Cleveland Foundation
1921 Author, Parties, Politics and People
1922 Author, The Cleveland Crime Survey
1923-1928 Associate Professor of Government, Columbia University
1926 Editor and co-author, The Missouri Crime Survey
1926-1927 Research Director, New York State Crime Commission
1928-1954 Professor of Public Law, Columbia University
1929 Author, Politics and Criminal Prosecution
1930 Author, Our Criminal Courts
1931-1933 Research Director, Committee on the Administration of Justice, New York State
1932 Author, Tribunes of the People Speechwriter and advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt during 1932 Presidential Campaign
1933 Assistant Secretary of State
1933-1937 Editor, Today (magazine)
1937-1968 Contributing Editor, Newsweek (magazine)
1938 Author, Are We Movie-Made?
1939 Author, After Seven Years
1945 Author, The Hays Office
1949 Author, Twenty-Seven Masters of Politics
1950 Author, Valley Authorities
1952 Author, How To Keep Our Liberty
1955 Author, What Price Federal Reclamation
1956 Co-author, The Upper Colorado Project
1958 Author, Political Responsibility of Business Men
1962 Author, The American Century of John C. Lincoln Author, The Republican Opportunity
1966 Author, The First New Deal
1975 Died, Phoenix, Arizona
Container List
- DIARIES AND TELEPHONE BOOKS, 1931-1940 (Box 1)
  Telephone books; Appointment book, 1931; holograph diary, January to June 1933; secretary's diary, January to July 1933; and journal, 1936-1940, arranged as listed
  - Telephone books (Box 1)
  - Appointment book, 1931
  - Holograph diary, January-June 1933
  - Diary kept by secretary, January-July 1933
  - Journal, 1936-1940
- GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1912-1969 (Boxes 2-62)
  Correspondence arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent
  - Aanonsen, Nils, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Helen Page, 1933 (Folder 2)
  - Abbott, Horatio J., 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Abeles, Joles, 1951-1965 (Folder 4)
  - Abernathy, R. A., 1955 (Folder 5)
  - Abernathy, U. A., 1921-1927 (Folder 6)
  - Abramson, M. E., 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Ackerman, Carl W., 1932-1934 (Folder 7)
  - Ackerman, William C., 1947 (Folder 9)
  - Adair, Rex, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - Adams, Alva B., 1937 (Folder 11)
  - Adams, Edgar E., 1933 (Folder 12)
  - Adams, E. J., 1941 (Folder 13)
  - Adams, Franklin P., 1936 (Folder 14)
  - Adams, Russell H., 1943 (Folder 15)
  - Adams, Samuel Hopkins, 1939 (Folder 16)
  - Adams, Sherman, 1952 (Folder 17)
  - Adams, Wayne, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Adelson, Shirley, 1937-1939 (Folder 19)
  - Adler, Mortimer J., 1939-1955 (Folder 20)
  - Adney, E. T., 1941 (Folder 21)
  - Affleck, Benjamin Franklin, 1931-1943 (Folder 22)
  - Aiken, H. W., 1934 (Folder 23)
  - Ailshie, Margaret Cobb, 1949-1951 (Folder 24)
  - Akers, Kenneth W., 1943-1964 (Folder 25)
  - Alberts, B. A., 1934 (Folder 26)
  - Albro, M. Z., 1934 (Folder 27)
  - Alcott, G. F., 1952 (Folder 28)
  - Alderman, E. A., 1936 (Folder 29)
  - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1938 (Folder 30)
  - Alessandroni, Mrs. Venan J., 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Alexander, H. S., 1933 (Folder 32)
  - Alexander, Harry W., 1943 (Folder 33)
  - Alexander, Lottie Gray, 1932 (Folder 34)
  - Alexander, Margaret C., 1919 (Folder 35)
  - Alexander, Will W., 1937 (Folder 36)
  - Alexandre, Emanuel, 1934 (Folder 37)
  - Alger, Bruce, 1964 (Folder 38)
  - Alger, George W., 1930 (Folder 39)
  - Allan, John J., 1937 (Folder 40)
  - Allen, Carolyn E., 1929-1930 (Folder 41)
  - Allen, Florence E., 1944 (Folder 42)
  - Allen, Frederick L., 1937 (Folder 43)
  - Allen, George E., 1950 (Folder 44)
  - Allen, H. W., n.d. (Folder 45)
  - Allen, Helen, 1952 (Folder 46)
  - Allen, J. Weston, 1928-1929 (Folder 47)
  - Allen, Robert McDowell, 1934 (Folder 48)
  - Allen, Robert S., 1936 (Folder 49)
  - Allen, Sophie E., 1915 (Folder 50)
  - Allen, William, 1931 (Folder 51)
  - Allen, William H., 1961 (Folder 52)
  - Allin, Cephas D., 1919-1927 (Folder 53)
  - Allison, Lelah, 1952 (Folder 54)
  - Allott, Guy, 1936-1937 (Folder 55)
  - Alsop, Joseph W., 1936 (Folder 56)
  - Alston, Robert C., 1932-1933 (Folder 57)
  - Althouse, C. E., 1933 (Folder 58)
  - Altschul, Frank, 1932-1938 (Folder 59)
  - American Political Science Association, 1932 (Folder 60)
  - Ames, John D., 1942-1949 (Folder 61)
  - Amidon, Bevlah, 1929 (Folder 62)
  - Ammidon, Hoyt, 1957-1961 (Folder 63)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Alan L., 1958 (Folder 64)
  - Anderson, B. M., 1932 (Folder 65)
  - Anderson, C. Vivian, 1951 (Folder 66)
  - Anderson, Clinton P., 1946-1962 (Folder 67)
  - Anderson, Frederick D., 1957 (Folder 68)
  - Anderson, J. E., 1938 (Folder 69)
  - Anderson, Patrick, 1966 (Folder 70)
  - Anderson, Richard J., 1963 (Folder 71)
  - Anderson, Sherwood, 1934-1936 (Folder 72)
  - Anderson, Stanton D., 1964 (Folder 73)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Walter M., 1951 (Folder 74)
  - Anderson, William, 1919-1930 (Folder 75)
  - Andrews, Carl M., 1955 (Folder 76)
  - Andrews, Paul, 1931 (Folder 77)
  - Andrews, T. Coleman, 1953 (Folder 78)
  - Angell, Ernest, 1937 (Folder 79)
  - Angly, Edward, 1951 (Folder 80)
  - Angoff, Charles, 1948 (Folder 81)
  - Ankeny, Marling J., 1961 (Folder 82)
  - Anthony, Alfred W., 1927 (Folder 83)
  - Anthony, Edward, 1954 (Folder 84)
  - Anthony, Samuel, 1957 (Folder 85)
  - Antin, Bessie, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appleby, Paul H., 1938 (Folder 2)
  - Appleton, Robert, 1931 (Folder 3)
  - Arbiter, Harold T., 1924 (Folder 4)
  - Arbuthnot, C. C., 1923-1925 (Folder 5)
  - Archer, R. J., 1941-1942 (Folder 6)
  - Arends, L. C., 1957 (Folder 7)
  - Angraves, N. E., 1954 (Folder 8)
  - Arkell, W. C., 1934 (Folder 9)
  - Armistead, George H., 1939-1940 (Folder 10)
  - Armistead, M. W., III, 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Armitage, Charles H., 1933 (Folder 12)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, 1938 (Folder 13)
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1934 (Folder 14)
  - Arneson, A. L., 1934 (Folder 15)
  - Arnold, O. J., 1941 (Folder 16)
  - Arnold, Thurman, 1938 (Folder 17)
  - Aronson, Moses J., 1941-1943 (Folder 18)
  - Arpin, A. L., 1954 (Folder 19)
  - Ardsdale, Henry Van, 1933 (Folder 20)
  - Arthur, Harry A., 1937 (Folder 21)
  - Artman, Joseph M., 1931 (Folder 22)
  - Ashcroft, Mrs. Charles D., 1923 (Folder 23)
  - Associated Newspapers, Inc., 1955-1961 (Folder 24)
  - Astor, Vincent, 1934-1960. Includes letter from Helen Astor, n.d. (Folder 25)
  - Atherton, P. L., 1930 (Folder 26)
  - Atkinson, Herschel C., 1950 (Folder 27)
  - Atkinson, Raymond C., 1922-1929 (Folder 28)
  - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1932 (Folder 29)
  - Auchterlonie, Helen, 1964-1965 (Folder 30)
  - Auer, Charles I., n.d. (Folder 31)
  - Auerbach, Richard D., 1963 (Folder 32)
  - Ausen, Arne, 1934 (Folder 33)
  - Austin, Edwin C., 1960 (Folder 34)
  - Automobile Club, 1922 (Folder 35)
  - Averill, Vincent, 1933 (Folder 36)
  - Avery, Sewell, 1942-1954 (Folder 37)
  - Awalt, F. Gloyd, 1936 (Folder 38)
  - Axtell, Silas B., 1934 (Folder 39)
  - Babando, Joseph A., 1965 (Folder 40)
  - Bach, E. L., 1936 (Folder 41)
  - Bachrach, Louis Fabian, 1960 (Folder 42)
  - Baer, George P., 1922-1936 (Folder 43)
  - Bagger, Eugene S., 1917-1941 (Folder 44)
  - Baggs, William C., 1961 (Folder 45)
  - Bailey, Forrest, 1931 (Folder 46)
  - Bailey, Phillip W., 1948 (Folder 47)
  - Bair, F. H., 1933 (Folder 48)
  - Baker, Howard H., 1963 (Folder 49)
  - Baker, J. Eugene, Jr., 1941 (Folder 50)
  - Baker, James H., 1962-1964 (Folder 51)
  - Baker, Newton D., 1929-1940 (Folder 52)
  - Baker, William R., Jr., 1943 (Folder 53)
  - Bakhmeteff, Boris A., 1941 (Folder 54)
  - Balch, Albert, 1965 (Folder 55)
  - Balch, Earle H., 1931-1938 (Folder 56)
  - Baldwin, Joseph Clark, III, 1937 (Folder 57)
  - Baldwin, Raymond S., 1948 (Folder 58)
  - Baldwin, Roger N., 1931 (Folder 59)
  - Baldwin Wallace College Library, 1951 (Folder 60)
  - Ballantine, Arthur A., 1939-1952 (Folder 61)
  - Balmer, Edwin, 1934 (Folder 62)
  - Bane, Frank, 1943 (Folder 63)
  - Bang, Edward, 1955 (Folder 64)
  - Banner, Franklin, 1937 (Folder 65)
  - Banta, Edwin P., 1939 (Folder 66)
  - Banton, Joab H., 1931 (Folder 67)
  - Barbara, M., 1941-1942 (Folder 68)
  - Barber, Thomas V., 1933 (Folder 69)
  - Barbre, William T., 1937 (Folder 70)
  - Barclay, Thomas S., 1932-1959 (Folder 71)
  - Barden, C. A., 1955 (Folder 72)
  - Barger, Harry S., 1943 (Folder 73)
  - Bargeron, Carlisle, 1936-1939 (Folder 74)
  - Barker, Charles A., 1955 (Folder 75)
  - Barker, Edwin H., 1941 (Folder 76)
  - Barkhausen, H. N., 1932-1933 (Folder 77)
  - Barkley, Alben W., 1948 (Folder 78)
  - Barley, Rex, 1965 (Folder 79)
  - Barlow, Channing, 1966 (Folder 80)
  - Barnard College, Columbia University, 1917-1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Barnard, Harry, 1945-1951 (Folder 2)
  - Barnard, John B., 1954 (Folder 3-4)
  - Barnard, Dr. Robert, 1956 (Folder 5)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1936-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Barnes, William R., 1937 (Folder 7)
  - Barnett, Rabbi 1933 (Folder 8)
  - Barnum, Corwin, 1953 (Folder 9)
  - Barnum, Frank J., 1933 (Folder 10)
  - Barnum, J. Elmer, 1932-1942 (Folder 11)
  - Barnum, Mrs. T. R., 1963 (Folder 12)
  - Barony, Hobcaw, n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Barr, Henry M., 1940-1941 (Folder 14)
  - Barr, Ralph, 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Barrere, W. E., 1965 (Folder 16)
  - Barrett, Edward F., 1952 (Folder 17)
  - Barrett, Edward W., 1937-1961 (Folder 18)
  - Barriger, John W., 1963 (Folder 19)
  - Barrows, Sarah T., 1918 (Folder 20)
  - Barton, Bruce, 1936-1963 (Folder 21)
  - Bartunek, Emil A., 1933-1935 (Folder 22)
  - Baruch, Bernard M., 1932-1960 (Folder 23)
  - Baruch, Herman B., 1936 (Folder 24)
  - Bashford, J. C., 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Bassett, James, 1965 (Folder 26)
  - Batchelor, Bronson, 1943 (Folder 27)
  - Bates, Frank G., 1917-1924 (Folder 28)
  - Bathke, David, 1965 (Folder 29)
  - Battle, George Gordon, 1931 (Folder 30)
  - Battle, Kemp D., 1933 (Folder 31)
  - Bauer, Charles C., 1943 (Folder 32)
  - Baumer, William H., 1959-1960 (Folder 33)
  - Baumes, Cales H., 1930 (Folder 34)
  - Baumgardner, Fred J., 1963 (Folder 35)
  - Baumhoff, George W., 1932 (Folder 36)
  - Baxter, Lewis L., 1933 (Folder 37)
  - Bazinet, John L., 1942 (Folder 38)
  - Beard, Charles A., 1914-1945 (Folder 39)
  - Beard, Charles E., 1943-1964 (Folder 40)
  - Beardsley, W. W., 1931-1934 (Folder 41)
  - Beaubaire, Stanley, 1938 (Folder 42)
  - Beaverbrook, Lord, 1950 (Folder 43)
  - Beazell, W. P., n.d. (Folder 44)
  - Becker, Margaret F., 1937 (Folder 45)
  - Beecher, Daniel, 1931 (Folder 46)
  - Beer, Henry Ward, 1932 (Folder 47)
  - Beer, Thomas, 1934 (Folder 48)
  - Beetson, Fred, 1938 (Folder 49)
  - Behan, Joseph C., 1941 (Folder 50)
  - Behney, Mrs. Charles Clyde, 1953 (Folder 51)
  - Behrman, Marguerite B., 1941 (Folder 52)
  - Behrman, Z. N., 1936 (Folder 53)
  - Belding, Donald, 1956-1957 (Folder 54)
  - Bell, A. Daniel, 1937 (Folder 55)
  - Bell, Elliott V., 1943 (Folder 56)
  - Bell, Frank T., 1934 (Folder 57)
  - Bell, J. Heywood, 1957 (Folder 58)
  - Bell, Robert S., 1960 (Folder 59)
  - Bellamy, George A., 1938 (Folder 60)
  - Bellamy, Paul, 1934-1954 (Folder 61)
  - Belmont, Alan H., 1963 (Folder 62)
  - Bemis, William H., 1950 (Folder 63)
  - Bender, Arthur, 1937 (Folder 64)
  - Bender, George H., 1921-1955 (Folder 65-66)
  - Bender, R. J., 1932 (Folder 67)
  - Benedum, M. L., 1932 (Folder 68)
  - Benesch, Alfred A., n.d. (Folder 69)
  - Bennett, E. L., 1919 (Folder 70)
  - Bennett, Emmett L., 1965-1966 (Folder 71)
  - Bennett, Wallace F., 1950-1962 (Folder 72)
  - Benson, Elmer A., 1943 (Folder 73)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft, 1954-1965 (Folder 74)
  - Benson, George C. S., 1955-1963 (Folder 75)
  - Bentley, Alvin M., 1960 (Folder 76)
  - Benton, E. J., 1917 (Folder 77)
  - Benton, W. B., 1936 (Folder 78)
  - Bentson, Kenneth G., 1958-1963 (Folder 79)
  - Benz, Walter G., 1943 (Folder 80)
  - Berea News, 1933 (Folder 81)
  - Berg, Mrs. Gerhard, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Berge, Albert, 1941 (Folder 2)
  - Berger, John A., 1941 (Folder 3)
  - Berle, A. A., 1932-1937 (Folder 4)
  - Berlin, Richard, 1938 (Folder 5)
  - Bernard, Jessie, 1954-1955 (Folder 6)
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1937-1965 (Folder 7)
  - Bernstein, Pearl, 1936 (Folder 8)
  - Bernstein, S. L., 1934 (Folder 9)
  - Berry, George L., 1936 (Folder 10)
  - Berry, John, 1936 (Folder 11)
  - Berry, M. H., 1937 (Folder 12)
  - Berry, M. M., 1926-1932 (Folder 13)
  - Berry, M. W., 1956 (Folder 14)
  - Bertrana, Raymond, 1938-1939 (Folder 15)
  - Best, Richard A., 1965 (Folder 16)
  - Best, Robert D., 1961 (Folder 17)
  - Bettman, Alfred, 1932-1933 (Folder 18)
  - Betts, Joseph, 1952 (Folder 19)
  - Bevis, Howard L., 1933 (Folder 20)
  - Beyle, Herman C., 1931-1934 (Folder 21)
  - Biben, Joseph H., 1938 (Folder 22)
  - Biddle, D. M., 1934 (Folder 23)
  - Biddle, Francis, 1942 (Folder 24)
  - Biegal, Herman C., 1932 (Folder 25)
  - Bigbee, North, 1937 (Folder 26)
  - Bigelow, Eugene K., 1934 (Folder 27)
  - Biggers, John D., 1936-1939 (Folder 28)
  - Billi, Giovanni, 1936 (Folder 29)
  - Billikopf, Jacob, 1931 (Folder 30)
  - Bilter, Margery, 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Bingay, Malcolm W., 1950 (Folder 32)
  - Bingham, Robert W., 1932 (Folder 33)
  - Birch, S. M., 1943 (Folder 34)
  - Bird, Caroline, 1966 (Folder 35)
  - Bird, Elisha Brown, n.d. (Folder 36)
  - Bisno, Julius, 1937 (Folder 37)
  - Bistor, J. E., 1934 (Folder 38)
  - Bittinger, Donald S., 1963 (Folder 39)
  - Bittum, Harriet, 1921 (Folder 40)
  - Black, Mrs. Arla Robin, 1934 (Folder 41)
  - Black, George, 1933 (Folder 42)
  - Black, Marvin M., 1939 (Folder 43)
  - Black, Mrs. Theda L., n.d. (Folder 44)
  - Black, Shirley Temple, 1960 (Folder 45)
  - Black, William Harman, 1931-1964 (Folder 46)
  - Blackburn, Katherine C., 1936 (Folder 47)
  - Blackett, H. W., 1941 (Folder 48)
  - Blackman, Samuel G., 1952 (Folder 49)
  - Blakely, Paul L., 1940 (Folder 50)
  - Blaker, Mrs. Ernest, 1933 (Folder 51)
  - Blair, Henry T., 1933 (Folder 52)
  - Blair, Ida, 1924 (Folder 53)
  - Blake, Gibson, 1930 (Folder 54)
  - Blandy, I. C., 1936 (Folder 55)
  - Bliss, Ray C., 1962-1966 (Folder 56)
  - Bloch, Robert G., 1939 (Folder 57)
  - Block, Paul, 1938 (Folder 58)
  - Blodgett, John W., 1942 (Folder 59)
  - Bluestone, Mr. H. I., 1933 (Folder 60)
  - Blum, Herman, 1951 (Folder 61)
  - Blumenthal, Eugene, 1943 (Folder 62)
  - Blumenthal, Henry, 1964 (Folder 63)
  - Boasberg, Rickie, 1933 (Folder 64)
  - Boate, John W., 1954 (Folder 65)
  - Boas, Franz, 1936 (Folder 66)
  - Boddie, William W., 1949 (Folder 67)
  - Boddy, Manchester, 1949 (Folder 68)
  - Bodyfish, Morton, 1936-1965 (Folder 69)
  - Bodine, Stanley R., 1939 (Folder 70)
  - Boer, Benjamin C., 1933 (Folder 71)
  - Boettiger, John, 1942 (Folder 72)
  - Boettiger, Mrs. J. H., 1964 (Folder 73)
  - Bogert, Stanley, 1921 (Folder 74)
  - Bogue, Arthur Hoyt, 1933 (Folder 75)
  - Bohlmann, Elsie, 1951 (Folder 76)
  - Bohn, Frank, 1933-1953 (Folder 77)
  - Bohn, William E., 1931-1960 (Folder 78)
  - Bohner, Edward E., 1921 (Folder 79)
  - Boissard, George R., 1943 (Folder 80)
  - Bolin, William, 1930 (Folder 81)
  - Bolton, Oliver P., 1964 (Folder 82)
  - Bomer, Charles F., 1934-1936 (Folder 83)
  - Bonbright, James C., 1930-1937 (Folder 84)
  - Bond, Horace M., 1955 (Folder 85)
  - Bond, Merritt, 1933 (Folder 86)
  - Bonds, Dr. A. B., Jr., 1957-1960 (Folder 87)
  - Bonds, Mrs. A. B., Jr., 1957 (Folder 88)
  - Bonsey, Charles, 1952 (Folder 89)
  - Bonsey, John, 1933-1941 (Folder 90)
  - Booker, E. D., 1939 (Folder 91)
  - Booth, Harry R., 1934 (Folder 92)
  - Booth, James W., 1930 (Folder 93)
  - Booth, Robert J., 1934 (Folder 94)
  - Borah, William E., 1934-1936 (Folder 95)
  - Borchard, Edwin M., 1932-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Boreman, Arthur I., 1941 (Folder 2)
  - Borg, Lester Skene, 1963 (Folder 3)
  - Borg, Madeline, n.d. (Folder 4)
  - Bork, Larry S., 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Borschenstein, Harold, 1938 (Folder 6)
  - Bosak, Miles, 1937 (Folder 7)
  - Bosted, John C., 1958-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Boston, Charles A., 1932 (Folder 9)
  - Bottin, Ronald, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Boulware, Lemuel E., 1948-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Boulware, L. R., 1938 (Folder 12)
  - Bourjaily, M. F., 1921-1941 (Folder 13)
  - Bourke, Walter, 1933 (Folder 14)
  - Bouriller, G. Lee, 1938 (Folder 15)
  - Boutin, Cladwin, May 9, 1934 (Folder 16)
  - Boutwell, W. D., 1934 (Folder 17)
  - Bowers, Glen A., 1933 (Folder 18)
  - Bow, Frank T., 1955-1958 (Folder 19)
  - Bowers, Robert E., 1962-1963 (Folder 20)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1940-1947 (Folder 21)
  - Bowman, Elizabeth M., 1922 (Folder 22)
  - Bowman, Geline MacDonald, 1933 (Folder 23)
  - Bowman, J. Warren, 1943 (Folder 24)
  - Bowman, LeRoy, 1929 (Folder 25)
  - Bowman, William J., 1964 (Folder 26)
  - Bow, Clara, 1960-1963 (Folder 27)
  - Bowers, Robert E., 1963 (Folder 28)
  - Bowser, W. F., 1933 (Folder 29)
  - Bowser, Willard P., 1935 (Folder 30)
  - Boyd, Henry, 1932 (Folder 31)
  - Boyd, Stanley H., 1964 (Folder 32)
  - Boyle, Thomas A., 1965-1966 (Folder 33)
  - Boynton, William E., 1918-1937 (Folder 34)
  - Bradford, Larned G., 1960 (Folder 35)
  - Bradford, Ned, 1956 (Folder 36)
  - Bradford, Tex, 1945 (Folder 37)
  - Bradlee, Benjamin C., 1966 (Folder 38)
  - Bradley, Richards M., 1935 (Folder 39)
  - Bradley, Vernon S., 1934 (Folder 40)
  - Bradshaw, Elizabeth B., 1933 (Folder 41)
  - Brady, Matthew, 1934 (Folder 42)
  - Brady, William A., 1937 (Folder 43)
  - Brady, William C., 1956 (Folder 44)
  - Brainerd, Eveline W., 1926 (Folder 45)
  - Branch, Harllee, 1962-1963 (Folder 46)
  - Brandt, Mrs. Carl, 1951-1964 (Folder 47)
  - Brandt, Carol, 1964 (Folder 48)
  - Brandt, Fred, 1936 (Folder 49)
  - Branham, Vernon C., 1932 (Folder 50)
  - Braniff, T. E., 1951 (Folder 51)
  - Brannon, Robert L., Jr., 1963 (Folder 52)
  - Branscomb, Dr. Harvie, 1959 (Folder 53)
  - Branson, J. H., Jr., 1933 (Folder 54)
  - Brasol, Boris, 1929 (Folder 55)
  - Braun, Lewis H., 1939 (Folder 56)
  - Braun, T. W., 1939 (Folder 57)
  - Braun, Wilhelm A., 1943 (Folder 58)
  - Breckenridge, H. C., 1933 (Folder 59)
  - Breckenridge, Margaret Hatfield, 1931 (Folder 60)
  - Breeding, Corrinne, 1957 (Folder 61)
  - Breen, Joseph I., 1937-1953 (Folder 62)
  - Brehmer, Robert G., 1934 (Folder 63)
  - Brennan, Robert, 1940 (Folder 64)
  - Brennan, Thomas M., 1956 (Folder 65)
  - Brett, Allen, 1938 (Folder 66)
  - Brettiger, Anna, 1935 (Folder 67)
  - Bretton, Max, 1933 (Folder 68)
  - Brewer, Basil, 1935 (Folder 69)
  - Brewster, Owen, 1952 (Folder 70)
  - Brewster, William T., 1943 (Folder 71)
  - Brichner, Barnett K., 1936 (Folder 72)
  - Bricker, Mrs. John W., 1943 (Folder 73)
  - Bricker, John W., 1940-1966 (Folder 74)
  - Bridge, Lionel, 1942 (Folder 75)
  - Bridges, Styles, 1954 (Folder 76)
  - Briegel, Jesse, 1933 (Folder 77)
  - Brigham, Robert M., 1963 (Folder 78)
  - Briney, Reuben, 1937 (Folder 79)
  - Brisbane, Arthur, 1935-1936 (Folder 80)
  - Bristol, Lee H., 1936-1937 (Folder 81)
  - Broderick, Edwin B., 1962 (Folder 82)
  - Brody, I. James, 1936 (Folder 83)
  - Brogan, D. W., 1960 (Folder 84)
  - Brokaw, Claire Booth, 1933 (Folder 85)
  - Bromfield, Lewis, 1938 (Folder 86)
  - Brooks, Herbert, 1935 (Folder 87)
  - Brookhart, Smith W., 1934 (Folder 88)
  - Brooko, Arthur J. H., 1945 (Folder 89)
  - Brooko, Mrs. Frederick, 1931 (Folder 90)
  - Brooko, Harry W., 1965 (Folder 91)
  - Broom, Ronald S., 1958 (Folder 92)
  - Brophy, Bernadine, 1960 (Folder 93)
  - Brophy, Frank Cullen, 1960 (Folder 94)
  - Browdy, Phillip, 1933 (Folder 95)
  - Brown, Alexander N., 1939 (Folder 96)
  - Brown, Caxton, 1941 (Folder 97)
  - Brown, C. M., 1943 (Folder 98)
  - Brown, Clarence J., 1930-1954 (Folder 99)
  - Brown, Edmund G., 1958-1961 (Folder 100)
  - Brown, Everett S., 1920-1929 (Folder 101)
  - Brown, George Rothwell, 1937-1939 (Folder 102)
  - Brown, Harry Gunnison, 1960 (Folder 103)
  - Brown, James L., 1961 (Folder 104)
  - Brown, Jesse R., 1963 (Folder 105)
  - Brown, Larue, 1933 (Folder 106)
  - Brown, Lewis H., 1936-1951 (Folder 107)
  - Brown, Mabel C., 1956 (Folder 108)
  - Brown, Marie T., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Mark A., 1950 (Folder 2)
  - Brown, Pearl, 1934 (Folder 3)
  - Brown, Thad H., 1933 (Folder 4)
  - Brown, Walter T., 1933 (Folder 5)
  - Brown, William R., 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Brown, William W., 1956 (Folder 7)
  - Brownell, Herbert, Jr., 1948-1952 (Folder 8)
  - Brownfeld, Allan C., 1965 (Folder 9)
  - Brownson, Charles B., 1960 (Folder 10)
  - Broyhill, Joel T., 1958 (Folder 11)
  - Bruce, A. D., 1957 (Folder 12)
  - Bruce, David K. E., 1934 (Folder 13)
  - Bruce, H. Addington, 1954 (Folder 14)
  - Bruce, Haynes, 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Bruce, Harold L., 1933 (Folder 16)
  - Bruere, Henry, 1932-1939 (Folder 17)
  - Bruner, Raymond A., 1933 (Folder 18)
  - Brunet, Robert D., 1963 (Folder 19)
  - Bruno, Frank J., 1930 (Folder 20)
  - Brunsdale, Anne, 1965 (Folder 21)
  - Brush, Lewis H., 1932-1939 (Folder 22)
  - Bryan, James W., 1930 (Folder 23)
  - Bryan, Tennant, 1955 (Folder 24)